Guide to the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, Reference Service Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Public Services records, 2006-2008; Accession 2009-A-068
  - Correspondence
    - U - Wh, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Wi - Zz, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Copy/Scan/Media Orders, 2006-2007
    - A - Bz, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - C - Ez, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - f- Iz, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - J - Lz, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - M - Oz, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - P - Sz, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - T - Zz, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Application to Examine, 2006-2007
    - A - Lz, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - M - Zz, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Photography Agreement, 2007-2008
    - A - Zz, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - f. Wald Agreements, 2007-2008
    - A - Zz, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Facsimile Reproductions Agreement, 2007-2008
    - A - Zz, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Authorization to Publish, 2007-2008
    - A - Zz, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Calls Slips, 2006-2007
    - Publication, Archive (RU) and Mircrofilm/fiche Slips, 2006-2007 (Box 5)
    - Manuscript (MS) Slips, 2006-2007 (Box 6)
- Public Services records, 2007-2009; Accession 2010-A-026
  - Correspondence, 2007-2008
    - AA - AL (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - AM - AZ (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - BAA - BAZ (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - BB - BE (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - BF - BN (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - BO - BQ (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - BR (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - BS - BZ (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - CAA - CAP (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - CAR - CAZ (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - CB - CH (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - CI - CN (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - CO (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - CP - CZ (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - DA - DD (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - DE - DN (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - DP - DZ (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - E (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - FA - FE (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - FH - FZ (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - G - GI (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - GL - GO (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - GR - GZ (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - HAA - HAN (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - HAO - HAZ (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - HB - HH (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - HI - HP (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - HS - HZ (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - ILL (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - I (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - J (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - KA - KE (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - KH - KZ (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - LA (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - LE - LI (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - LO - LZ (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - MAA - MAQ (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - MAR - MAZ (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - MC (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - ME - MI (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - MO (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - MR - MZ (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - NA - NH (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - NI - NZ (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - OA - OZ (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - PA (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - PB - PH (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - PI - PO (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - PR - PZ (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Q - RE (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - RF - RN (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - RO - RZ (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - SA (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - SC (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - SE - SH (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - SI - SM (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - SN - SS (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - ST - STE (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - STI - SZ (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - TA - TH (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - TI - TZ (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - U - V (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - WA - WD (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - WE - WH (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - WI (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - WO - WZ (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - X - Z (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Photography Agreements, 2008-2009
    - A - L (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - M - Z (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Application to Examine, 2007-2008
    - A - K (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - L - Z (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Reprographic Order Forms, 2007-2008
    - A- B (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - C - D (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - E - G (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - H - J (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - K - L (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - M - N (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - O - Q (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - R (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - S (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - T - V (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - W - Z (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Publication, Archive (RU) and Microfilm/fiche Slips, 2007-2008 (Box 6)
  - Manuscript (MS) Slips, 2007-2008 (Box 7)
  - Reference Desk Records, 2008-2009 (Box 8)
  - Patron Sign In Sheets
    - July -September 2008 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - October - December 2008 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - January - March 2009 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - April - June 2009 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Contact Reference Sheet
    - July - August 2008 (Box 8, Folder 87)
- Public Services records, 2008-2009; Accession 2011-A-009
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2045
  - Reference Correspondence 2009R
    - A - ALD (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ALE - AM (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - AND-AZ (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - B - BAR (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - BAS - BEN (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - BEO - BIX (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - BLA - BOW (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - BOX - BRE (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - BRI - BUH (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - BUI - BZ (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - CA - CAR (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - CAS - CHAN (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - CHAP - CHU (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - CI - COO (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - COP - CZ (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - D - DEM (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - DEN - DOR (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - DOS - DZ (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - EA - ELL (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - ELM - EV (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - F - FIS (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - FIX - FRAS (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - FRA - FUN (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - G - GH (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - GI - GO (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - GR - GW (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - HA - HAM (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - HAN - HAY (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - HE - HIR (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - HOB - HOW (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - HOV - HY (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - ILL (AFU - NTA) (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - ILL (OKU - ZYU) (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - I (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - JA - JIM (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - JO - JU (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - KA - KELL (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - KELM - KIT (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - KL - KO (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - KR - KY (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - L - LEN (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - LEP - LIN (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - LIP - LOR (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - LOT - LY (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - M - MARQ (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - MARR - MAZ (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - McA - McM (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - ME - MID (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - MIL - MIT (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - MIY - MON (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - MOO - MP (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - MU - MY (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - N (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - O (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - P - PAU (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - PAV - PER (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - PET - POR (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - POT - PUL (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Q - REN (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - RES - ROT (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - ROR - RZ (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - S - SA (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - SC (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - SE - SHEP (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - SHER - SIN (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - SK - SPO (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - SOO-STI (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - STO - SZ (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - TAB - TEU (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - THAC - THUR (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - TI - TU (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - U - V (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - W - WAR (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - WAT - WES (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - WEX - WIE (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - WIL (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - WIN - WOF (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - WOL - WU (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - X - Z (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Reprographic Order Forms 2009R
    - A (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - B - BH (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - BI - BY (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - C - CH (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - CR (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - D (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - E (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - F (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - G (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - H (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - I - J (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - K (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - L (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - M (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - N (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - O-P (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - R (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - S (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - T (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - V- W (Box 6, Folder 99)
    - X -Z (Box 6, Folder 100)
    - Non-Disclosure Agreement Forms 2009R
      - 2009R (A - KI) (Box 6, Folder 103)
      - 2009R (KH - YO) (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - Application to Examine 2009R
    - A -K (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - L-Z (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - Manuscript Collections Call Slips 2009R (Box 7, Folder system_indicator_9ee40a447f1b333898588755e5c45fc9)
  - Yale Archives, Publication, and Microfilm/fische Call Slips 2009R (Box 8, Folder system_indicator_8daa2d86754c8754487e21d91fc616b9)
- Public Services records, 2008-2011; Accession 2012-A-001
  - Public Services Correspondence 2010R, 2009-2010
    - AA-AL (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - AM-AZ (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - BA-BAZ (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - BE-BL (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - BOD-BRA (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - BRE-BY (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - CA-CAZ (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - CEN-CHA (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - CHE-CHU (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - CI-COL (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - CON-CZ (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - DA-DEW (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - DI-DOY (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - DP-DY (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - E (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - F-FE (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - FI-FORG (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - FORS-FY (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - GA-GEO (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - GER-GIP (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - GL-GOO (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - GOR-GOU (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - GR-GRE (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - GRI-GU (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - HA-HAN (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - HAR-HAY (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - HE-HEU (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - HI-HOH (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - HOL-HU (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - I (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - ILL (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - J-JI (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - JO-JU (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - K-KEEN (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - KEH-KEY (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - KH-KL (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - KM-KY (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - L-LAP (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - LAR-LEI (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - LEL-LEW (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - LI-LIV (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - LO-LU (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - M-MAP (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - MAR-MAZ (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - MB-MC (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - MD-MI (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - MJ-MO (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - MP-MZ (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - N-NH (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - NI-NZ (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - OA-OQ (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - OR-OZ (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - PA (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - PB-PH (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - PP-Q (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - RA-RE (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - RF-RN (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - RO-ROOK (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - ROOS-ROS (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - RU-RY (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - SA (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - SB-SC (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - SE-SH (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - SI-SM (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - SN-SM (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - ST-STE (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - STI-SZ (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - T-TOB (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - TOL-TU (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - U (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - V (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - W-WAY (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - WE-WH (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - WI-WIT (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - WL-Y (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Z (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Photography Agreements 2011R, 2010-2011
    - A-L (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - M-Z (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Application to Publish Facsimile Reprographics 2011R, 2010-2011
    - A-Z (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Sign In Register 2011R, 2010-2011
    - JULY-AUGUST (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - SEPTEMBER-OCTOBER (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - NOVEMBER-DECEMBER (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - JANUARY-FEBRUARY (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - MARCH-APRIL (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - MAY-JUNE (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Reprographic Orders, 2009-2011
    - A-B (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - C-D (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - E-F (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - G (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - H-I (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - J-K (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - L (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - M-N (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - O-R (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - S (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - T-V (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - W-Z (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Application to Exam, 2009-2011
    - A-C (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - D-K (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - L-R (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - S-Z (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Shipping Memos, 2008-2010
    - FY 2008 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - FY 2009 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - FY 2010 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Public Services records, 2002-2010; Accession 2012-A-082
  - Sign-In Register 7/1/2009, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Sign-In Register 8/1/2009, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Sign-In Register 9/1/2009, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Sign-In Register 10/1/2009, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Sign-In Register 11/1/2009, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Sign-In Register 12/1/2009, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Sign-In Register 1/1/2010 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Sign-In Register 2/1/2010 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Sign-In Register 3/1/2010 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Sign-In Register 4/1/2010 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Sign-In Register 5/1/2010 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Sign-In Register 6/1/2010 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Non-Disclosure Agreement, A-Z, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Photography Agreement, A-L, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Photography Agreement, M-Z, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Access Agreements: Jane Roberts and Florence Wald, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Manuscript Collections Call Slips, 2010 (Box 2)
  - Archives, Microfilm, and Publications Call Slips, 2010 (Box 3)
  - Sign-In Register 7/2007, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Sign-In Register 8/2007, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Sign-In Register 9/2007, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Sign-In Register 10/2007, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Sign-In Register 11/2007, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Sign-In Register 12/2007, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Sign-In Register 1/2008 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Sign-In Register 2/2008 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Sign-In Register 3/2008 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Sign-In Register 4/2008 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Sign-In Register 5/2008 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Sign-In Register 6/2008 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Sign-In Register 7/2006, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Sign-In Register 8/2006, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Sign-In Register 9/2006, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Sign-In Register 10/2006, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Sign-In Register 11/2006, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Sign-In Register 12/2006, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Sign-In Register 1/2007 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Sign-In Register 2/2007 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Sign-In Register 3/2007 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Sign-In Register 4/2007 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Sign-In Register 5/2007 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Sign-In Register 6/2007 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Permission Letters: University Archives, 2007-2009 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Permission Letters: Manuscript Collections, 2007-2009 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Invoices, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Photography Agreement, A-Z, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Access Agreements: Richard C. Lee, Jane Roberts, and Florence Wald, 2002-2005 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Public Services records, 2005-2012; Accession 2012-A-098
  - Photography Agreements A-L, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Photography Agreements M-Z, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Reference Correspondence A-AL, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Reference Correspondence ALF-AP, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Reference Correspondence AR-AZ, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Reference Correspondence B-BAN, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Reference Correspondence BAP-BAR, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Reference Correspondence BAS-BEN, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Reference Correspondence BER-BJ, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Reference Correspondence BLA-BOW, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Reference Correspondence BOY-BROD, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Reference Correspondence BRON-BY, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Reference Correspondence C-CARB, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Reference Correspondence CARD-CARU, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Reference Correspondence CAS-CHU, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Reference Correspondence CIC-COD, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Reference Correspondence COH-COO, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Reference Correspondence COP-CUT, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Reference Correspondence D-DEM, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Reference Correspondence DEN-DOR, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Reference Correspondence DOS-DY, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Reference Correspondence E, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Reference Correspondence F-FIS, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Reference Correspondence FIT-FZ, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Reference Correspondence G-GH, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Reference Correspondence GI-GO, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Reference Correspondence GR-GU, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Reference Correspondence H-HARP, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Reference Correspondence HAR-HAY, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Reference Correspondence HEA-HIN, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Reference Correspondence HOB-HOL, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Reference Correspondence HOL-HOU, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Reference Correspondence HOW-HUG, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Reference Correspondence HUL-HY, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Reference Correspondence I, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Reference Correspondence ILL (AUM-IAY), 2011 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Reference Correspondence ILL (IDW-ZYU), 2011 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Reference Correspondence J-JOHNS, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Reference Correspondence JOHNST-JUR, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Reference Correspondence K-KEL, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Reference Correspondence KEM-KI, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Reference Correspondence KL-KO, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Reference Correspondence KR-KU, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Reference Correspondence L-LEN, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Reference Correspondence LEO-LIN, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Reference Correspondence LIO-LY, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Reference Correspondence M-MAP, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Reference Correspondence MAR-MAZ, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Reference Correspondence Mc, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Reference Correspondence ME-MIK, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Reference Correspondence MIL-MON, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Reference Correspondence MOO-MOU, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Reference Correspondence MU, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Reference Correspondence N-NEW, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Reference Correspondence NG-NY, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Reference Correspondence O, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Reference Correspondence P-PEE, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Reference Correspondence PEI-PF, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Reference Correspondence PIE-POS, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Reference Correspondence POT-PY, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Reference Correspondence Q, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Reference Correspondence R-RIE, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Reference Correspondence RIG-RON, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Reference Correspondence ROS-RY, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Reference Correspondence S-SA, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Reference Correspondence SC-SCHN, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Reference Correspondence SCHO-SCR, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Reference Correspondence SE-SIN, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Reference Correspondence SIA-SOM, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Reference Correspondence SOP-STI, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Reference Correspondence STO-SZ, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Reference Correspondence T-TH, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Reference Correspondence TI-TZ, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Reference Correspondence U-V, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Reference Correspondence W-WAR, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Reference Correspondence WAS-WES, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Reference Correspondence WH-WIL, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Reference Correspondence WIN-WU, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Reference Correspondence X-Z, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Reprographics Order Forms A-CH, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Reprographics Order Forms CI-D, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Reprographics Order Forms E-G, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Reprographics Order Forms H, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Reprographics Order Forms I-K, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Reprographics Order Forms L-MD, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Reprographics Order Forms ME-O, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Reprographics Order Forms P-R, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Reprographics Order Forms S, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Reprographics Order Forms T-V, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Reprographics Order Forms W-Z, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Applications to Examine A-C, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Applications to Examine D-K, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Applications to Examine L-R, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - Applications to Examine S-Z, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - Cancelled/On Hold Repro. Forms 903-1566, 2008-2011 (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - Cancelled/On Hold Repro. Forms 1601-2253, 2008-2011 (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Sign-In Register 2012, July-August 2011 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Sign-In Register 2012, September-October 2011 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Sign-In Register 2012, November-October 2011 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Sign-In Register 2012, January-February 2012 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Sign-In Register 2012 (register dicontinued here), March-May 2012 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Completed Office of Origin Call Slips YRG 2-3, Circa 2005-2011 (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Completed Office of Origin Call Slips YRG 4, Circa 2005-2011 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Completed Office of Origin Call Slips YRG 4 (cont.), Circa 2005-2011 (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Completed Office of Origin Call Slips YRG 5-12, Circa 2005-2011 (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Completed Office of Origin Call Slips YRG 13A-13H, Circa 2005-2011 (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - Completed Office of Origin Call Slips YRG 13I-13K, Circa 2005-2011 (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Completed Office of Origin Call Slips YRG 13L-13N, Circa 2005-2011 (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Completed Office of Origin Call Slips YRG 14-21, Circa 2005-2011 (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Completed Office of Origin Call Slips YRG 22-24, Circa 2005-2011 (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - Completed Office of Origin Call Slips YRG 25, Circa 2005-2011 (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Completed Office of Origin Call Slips YRG 26, Circa 2005-2011 (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Completed Office of Origin Call Slips YRG 26 (cont.), Circa 2005-2011 (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Completed Office of Origin Call Slips YRG (26 cont.), Circa 2005-2011 (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - Completed Office of Origin Call Slips YRG 27-32, Circa 2005-2011 (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Completed Office of Origin Call Slips YRG 34-46, Circa 2005-2011 (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Completed Office of Origin Call Slips YRG 1-12, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 117)
  - Completed Office of Origin Call Slips YRG 13-20, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 118)
  - Completed Office of Origin Call Slips YRG 21-27, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 119)
  - Completed Office of Origin Call Slips YRG 28-46, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 120)
  - FedEx Airbill Senders' Copies, 2010-2012 (Box 8, Folder 121)
  - Aeon Call Slips: Manuscripts Collections. Early-use, filed by MS# 1-239, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 122)
  - Aeon Call Slips: Manuscripts Collections. Early-use, filed by MS# 242-439, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 123)
  - Aeon Call Slips: Manuscripts Collections. Early-use, filed by MS# 440-579, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 124)
  - Aeon Call Slips: Manuscripts Collections. Early-use, filed by MS# 580-674, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 125)
  - Aeon Call Slips: Manuscripts Collections. Early-use, filed by MS# 683-1039, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 126)
  - Aeon Call Slips: Manuscripts Collections. Early-use, filed by MS# 1043-1367, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 127)
  - Aeon Call Slips: Manuscripts Collections. Early-use, filed by MS# 1367 (cont.)-1834, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 128)
  - Aeon Call Slips: Manuscripts Collections. Early-use, filed by MS# 1840-1970, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 129)
  - Aeon Call Slips: Record Units. Early-use, filed by RU# 1-58, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 130)
  - Aeon Call Slips: Record Units. Early-use, filed by RU# 65-276, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 131)
  - Aeon Call Slips: Record Units. Early-use, filed by RU# 281-1081, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 132)
  - Aeon Call Slips: Publications. Early-use, filed as Reference, Disseration, and Y Class Call # Y-Yz, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 133)
  - Aeon Call Slips: Microformat. Early-use, filed as Fiche, HM #17-263, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 134)